http://www.legluxe.com/pages/privacy

ShortsLeggingsArmsBodysuitsBodySlipsLegwear
Socks & Knee HighsThigh HighsTightsFoot ProtectorsSportMaternity
Your Privacy on Legluxe.com
This policy covers how Legluxe.com treats personal information that Legluxe.com collects and receives, including information related to your past use of Legluxe.com products. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Legluxe.com does not own or control or to people that Legluxe.com does not employ or manage.
Collecting Information
Legluxe.com collects personal information when you register with Legluxe.com, when you use Legluxe.com products, when you visit Legluxe.com pages or the pages of certain Legluxe.com partners, and when you enter promotions or sweepstakes. Legluxe.com may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies. When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address, birth date, gender, zip code, occupation, industry, and personal interests. Once you register with Legluxe.com and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. Legluxe.com automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, Legluxe.com cookie information, and the page you request. Legluxe.com uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.
Cookies
Legluxe.com may set and access Legluxe.com 'cookies' on your computer. Legluxe.com lets other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one.
Your Information
You can edit your Legluxe.com account information at any time. We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the Legluxe.com service, such as service announcements, administrative messages and the Legluxe.com Newsletter, that are considered part of your Legluxe.com account, without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them. You can delete your account by contacting Legluxe.com.
Confidentiality and Security
We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you.
Protecting Your Information
Legluxe.com does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances: We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with Legluxe.com under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help Legluxe.com communicate with you about offers from Legluxe.com and our marketing partners.
We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims; We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Legluxe.com's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.
We transfer information about you if Legluxe.com is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Legluxe.com will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.
Policy Updates
Legluxe.com may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your Legluxe.com account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.
Subscribe to our newsletter:
HelpReturns & RefundsShippingContact UsTrack OrderCompanyAbout UsOur StoryPrivacyCopyright
